<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<facts>
    <item>
	    <id>0</id>
	    <category>1</category>
	    <thumb>shakespeare</thumb>
	    <title>William Shakespeare</title>
	    <content>William Shakespeare (26 April 1564 (baptised) – 23 April 1616)[nb 1] was an English poet and playwright, widely regarded as the greatest writer in the English language and the world's pre-eminent dramatist.[1] He is often called England's national poet and the "Bard of Avon".[2][nb 2] His extant works, including some collaborations, consist of about 38 plays,[nb 3] 154 sonnets, two long narrative poems, two epitaphs on a man named John Combe, one epitaph on Elias James, and several other poems. His plays have been translated into every major living language and are performed more often than those of any other playwright.[3]</content>
    </item>
    <item>
	    <id>1</id>
	    <category>0</category>
	    <thumb>nyc</thumb>
	    <title>New York City</title>
	    <content>New York is the most populous city in the United States[13][14] and the center of the New York Metropolitan Area, one of the most populous urban agglomerations in the world.[15][16][17] The city is referred to as New York City or the City of New York[18] to distinguish it from the State of New York, of which it is a part.[19] A global power city,[20] New York exerts a significant impact upon commerce, finance, media, art, fashion, research, technology, education, and entertainment. The home of the United Nations Headquarters,[21] New York is an important center for international diplomacy[22] and has been described as the cultural capital of the world.[23][24][25][26]</content>
    </item>
    <item>
	    <id>2</id>
	    <category>0</category>
	    <thumb>beijing</thumb>
	    <title>Beijing</title>
	    <content>Beijing (pron.: /beɪˈdʒɪŋ/; Chinese: 北京; pinyin: Běijīng, [peɪ˨˩ t͡ɕiŋ˥]), sometimes romanized as Peking[4] (pron.: /piːˈkɪŋ/, /peɪˈkɪŋ/), is the capital of the People's Republic of China and one of the most populous cities in the world. The population as of 2012 was 20,693,000.[2] The metropolis, located in northern China, is governed as a direct-controlled municipality under the national government, with 14 urban and suburban districts and two rural counties.[5] Beijing Municipality is surrounded by Hebei Province with the exception of neighboring Tianjin Municipality to the southeast.[6]</content>
    </item>
    <item>
	    <id>3</id>
	    <category>0</category>
	    <thumb>london</thumb>
	    <title>London</title>
	    <content>London i/ˈlʌndən/ is the capital city of England and the United Kingdom, and the largest city, urban zone and metropolitan area in the United Kingdom, and the European Union by most measures.[note 1] Located on the River Thames, London has been a major settlement for two millennia, its history going back to its founding by the Romans, who named it Londinium.[4] London's ancient core, the City of London, largely retains its square-mile mediaeval boundaries. Since at least the 19th century, the name London has also referred to the metropolis developed around this core.[5] The bulk of this conurbation forms the London region[6] and the Greater London administrative area,[7][note 2] governed by the elected Mayor of London and the London Assembly.[8]</content>
    </item>
    <item>
	    <id>4</id>
	    <category>2</category>
	    <thumb>pine</thumb>
	    <title>Pine</title>
	    <content>Pines are trees in the genus Pinus (pron.: /ˈpiːnɪs/),[1] in the family Pinaceae. They are the only genus in the subfamily Pinoideae. There are about 115 species of pine, although different authorities accept between 105 and 125 species.</content>
    </item>
    <item>
	    <id>5</id>
	    <category>0</category>
	    <thumb>amsterdam</thumb>
	    <title>Amsterdam</title>
	    <content>Amsterdam (English /ˈæmstərdæm/; Dutch: [ˌɑmstərˈdɑm] ( listen)) is the largest city and the capital of the Netherlands. Its principal language is Dutch. The city's status as the capital of the nation is governed by the constitution.[6] Amsterdam has a population of 820,256 within city limits, an urban population of 1,209,419 and a metropolitan population of 2,289,762.[7] The city is located in the province of North Holland in the west of the country. It comprises the northern part of the Randstad, one of the larger conurbations in Europe, with a population of approximately 7 million.[8]</content>
    </item>
    <item>
	    <id>6</id>
	    <category>0</category>
	    <thumb>helsinki</thumb>
	    <title>Helsinki</title>
	    <content>Helsinki (Finnish pronunciation: [ˈhe̞l.siŋ.k̟i])  listen (help·info); Swedish: Helsingfors,  listen (help·info)) is the capital and largest city of Finland. It is in the region of Uusimaa, located in southern Finland, on the shore of the Gulf of Finland, an arm of the Baltic Sea. Helsinki has a population of 605,523 (28 February 2013),[3] an urban population of 1,159,211 (31 December 2011)[7] and a metropolitan population of 1,361,506, making it by far the most populous municipality and urban area in Finland. Helsinki is located some 80 kilometres (50 mi) north of Tallinn, Estonia, 400 kilometres (250 mi) east of Stockholm, Sweden, and 300 kilometres (190 mi) west of Saint Petersburg, Russia. Helsinki has close historical connections with these three cities.</content>
    </item>
    <item>
	    <id>7</id>
	    <category>1</category>
	    <thumb>michelangelo</thumb>
	    <title>Michelangelo</title>
	    <content>Michelangelo di Lodovico Buonarroti Simoni[1] (6 March 1475 – 18 February 1564), commonly known as Michelangelo (Italian pronunciation: [mikeˈlandʒelo]), was an Italian Renaissance sculptor, painter, architect, poet, and engineer who exerted an unparalleled influence on the development of Western art.[2] Despite making few forays beyond the arts, his versatility in the disciplines he took up was of such a high order that he is often considered a contender for the title of the archetypal Renaissance man, along with fellow Italian Leonardo da Vinci.</content>
    </item>
    <item>
	    <id>8</id>
	    <category>1</category>
	    <thumb>aristotle</thumb>
	    <title>Aristotle</title>
	    <content>Aristotle (Ancient Greek: Ἀριστοτέλης [aristotélɛːs], Aristotélēs) (384 BC – 322 BC)[1] was a Greek philosopher and polymath, a student of Plato and teacher of Alexander the Great. His writings cover many subjects, including physics, metaphysics, poetry, theater, music, logic, rhetoric, linguistics, politics, government, ethics, biology, and zoology. Together with Plato and Socrates (Plato's teacher), Aristotle is one of the most important founding figures in Western philosophy. Aristotle's writings were the first to create a comprehensive system of Western philosophy, encompassing morality, aesthetics, logic, science, politics, and metaphysics.</content>
    </item>
    <item>
	    <id>9</id>
	    <category>1</category>
	    <thumb>laozi</thumb>
	    <title>Laozi</title>
	    <content>Laozi (see other names and spelling variations; Chinese: 老子, English pronunciation: /ˌlaʊˈdzʌ/;[1][2] fl. 6th century BCE) was a philosopher of ancient China, best known as the author of the Tao Te Ching (often simply referred to as Laozi).[3] His association with the Tào Té Chīng has led him to be traditionally considered the founder of philosophical Taoism (pronounced as "Daoism"). He is also revered as a deity in most religious forms of Taoist philosophy, which often refers to Laozi as Taishang Laojun, or "One of the Three Pure Ones".</content>
    </item>
    <item>
	    <id>10</id>
	    <category>1</category>
	    <thumb>sjobs</thumb>
	    <title>Steve Jobs</title>
	    <content>Steven Paul "Steve" Jobs (/ˈdʒɒbz/; February 24, 1955 – October 5, 2011)[5][6] was an American entrepreneur[7] and inventor,[8] best known as the co-founder, chairman, and CEO of Apple Inc. Through Apple, he was widely recognized as a charismatic pioneer of the personal computer revolution[9][10] and for his influential career in the computer and consumer electronics fields, transforming "one industry after another, from computers and smartphones to music and movies..."[11] Jobs also co-founded and served as chief executive of Pixar Animation Studios; he became a member of the board of directors of The Walt Disney Company in 2006, when Disney acquired Pixar. Jobs was among the first to see the commercial potential of Xerox PARC's mouse-driven graphical user interface, which led to the creation of the Apple Lisa and, one year later, the Macintosh. He also played a role in introducing the LaserWriter, one of the first widely available laser printers, to the market.[12]</content>
    </item>
    <item>
	    <id>11</id>
	    <category>2</category>
	    <thumb>carnation</thumb>
	    <title>Carnation</title>
	    <content>Dianthus caryophyllus (Clove Pink) is a species of Dianthus. It is probably native to the Mediterranean region but its exact range is unknown due to extensive cultivation for the last 2,000 years. It is the wild ancestor of the garden carnation.[1][2][3][4]</content>
    </item>
    <item>
	    <id>12</id>
	    <category>2</category>
	    <thumb>grass</thumb>
	    <title>Grass</title>
	    <content>Grasses, or more technically graminoids, are monocotyledonous, usually herbaceous plants with narrow leaves growing from the base. They include the "true grasses", of the Poaceae (or Gramineae) family, as well as the sedges (Cyperaceae) and the rushes (Juncaceae). The true grasses include cereals, bamboo and the grasses of lawns (turf) and grassland. Sedges include many wild marsh and grassland plants, and some cultivated ones such as water chestnut (Eleocharis dulcis) and papyrus sedge (Cyperus papyrus). Uses for graminoids include food (as grain, sprouted grain, shoots or rhizomes), drink (beer, whisky, vodka), pasture for livestock, thatch, paper, fuel, clothing, insulation, construction, sports turf, basket weaving and many others.</content>
    </item>
    <item>
	    <id>13</id>
	    <category>2</category>
	    <thumb>corn</thumb>
	    <title>Corn</title>
	    <content>Maize (pron.: /ˈmeɪz/ mayz; Zea mays subsp. mays L, from Spanish: maíz after Taíno mahiz), known in some English-speaking countries as corn, is a large grain plant domesticated by indigenous peoples in Mesoamerica in prehistoric times. The leafy stalk produces ears which contain the grain, which are seeds called kernels. Maize kernels are used in cooking as a starch. The Olmec and Mayans cultivated it in numerous varieties throughout Mesoamerica, cooked, ground or processed through nixtamalization. Beginning about 2500 BC, the crop spread through much of the Americas.[1] The region developed a trade network based on surplus and varieties of maize crops. After European contact with the Americas in the late 15th and early 16th centuries, explorers and traders carried maize back to Europe and introduced it to other countries. Maize spread to the rest of the world because of its ability to grow in diverse climates. Sugar-rich varieties called sweet corn are usually grown for human consumption, while field corn varieties are used for animal feed and as chemical feedstocks.</content>
    </item>
</facts>